  {
    "lang": {
      "es": {
        "page": {
          "home": {
            "asideMenu": [
              {
                "desc": "Inicio",
                "goTo": "home",
                "icon": "home"
              },
              {
                "desc": "Acerca de mi",
                "goTo": "about",
                "icon": "user"
              },
              {
                "desc": "Porfolio",
                "goTo": "porfolio",
                "icon": "folder-tree"
              },
              {
                "desc": "Educación",
                "goTo": "education",
                "icon": "graduation-cap"
              }
            ],
            "sections": {
              "welcome": {
                "header": "bienvenido",
                "download": {
                  "desc": "Descargar CV"
                },
                "paragraphs": [
                  "<p>Te doy la bienvenida a mi página, acá encontrarás información adicional para conocerme mejor, además también encontrarás mi porfolio. </p>",
                  "<p>Soy Sergio Rivera, nací en Texas, Estados Unidos. Vivo en Buenos Aires, Argentina. En cuanto a mis estudios académicos, cuento con secundario completo, además de que a inicios de 2022 me recibí como Tecnico Superior en Programación en la UTN de General Pacheco, Buenos Aires, Argentina</p>"
                ]
              },
              "aboutMe": {
                "header": "Acerca de mi",
                "paragraphs": [
                  "La idea principal de esta sección es contestar unas preguntas frecuentes que hacen los recruiters/empleadores a nosotros los devs."
                ],
                "qa": [
                  {
                    "question": "¿Quién eres?",
                    "answer": "Soy un MERN/Full Stack developer, eso quiere decir que en las aplicaciones que desarrollo me encargo tanto del front end así como también de la lógica del back end."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "¿Cómo te describirías?",
                    "answer": "Me describiría como una persona curiosa, responsable y leal. Desde que era chico siempre me interesó todo lo relacionado con la tecnología, por eso disfruto de lo que hago."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "¿Por qué debería contratarte?",
                    "answer": "Desde mi punto de vista, me considero como alguien con gran potencial, además siempre que trabajo doy lo mejor de mi, con las mejores energías y con el mayor respeto hacia todos."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "¿Cuál es tu experiencia laboral?",
                    "answer": "Por el momento, ninguna. Hoy en día, para mí, es dificil encontrar oportunidades laborales. La mayoría de los cargos requieren personas con experiencia previa."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "¿Qué tecnologías sabes usar?",
                    "answer": "Entra las que más conozco podría destacar: React (Redux, Router, Hooks), MongoDB, Express, NodeJS, SQL Server, MySQL y ASP"
                  }
                ]
              },
              "education": {
                "header": "Historial Academico",
                "data": [
                  {
                    "date": {
                      "start": "2022",
                      "end": "2022"
                    },
                    "title": "Curso completo de React Hooks, Redux, Router",
                    "where": "Udemy",
                    "status": "completed",
                    "average": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "date": {
                      "start": "2020",
                      "end": "2022"
                    },
                    "title": "Tecnicatura Superior en Programación",
                    "where": "UTN FRGP, Argentina",
                    "status": "completed",
                    "average": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "date": {
                      "start": "2013",
                      "end": "2029"
                    },
                    "title": "Bachiller en Administración Contable",
                    "where": "Instituto Federico Dickens, Argentina",
                    "status": "completed",
                    "average": ""
                  }
                ]
              }
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "en": {
        "page": {
          "home": {
            "asideMenu": [
              {
                "desc": "Home",
                "goTo": "home",
                "icon": "home"
              },
              {
                "desc": "About Me",
                "goTo": "about",
                "icon": "user"
              },
              {
                "desc": "Porfolio",
                "goTo": "porfolio",
                "icon": "folder-tree"
              },
              {
                "desc": "Education",
                "goTo": "education",
                "icon": "graduation-cap"
              }
            ],
            "sections": {
              "welcome": {
                "header": "Welcome",
                "paragraphs": [
                  "<p>Welcome to my personal website!, here you may find aditional information about myself. This way people who visits this page might know more about me and also see my porfolio.</p>",
                  "<p>My name is Sergio Rivera, I was born in Texas, U.S. Right now I am living in Buenos Aires. I have completed high school and in beggings from 2020 I graduated from college with a Technician Programming Seniority degree at Universidad Tecnologica Nacional, General Pacheco, Buenos Aires, Argentina</p>"
                ],
                "download": {
                  "desc": "Download CV"
                }
              },
              "aboutMe": {
                "header": "About me",
                "paragraphs": [
                  "The principal idea from this section is answer a few frequent questions recruiters ask to devs."
                ],
                "qa": [
                  {
                    "question": "Who are you?",
                    "answer": "I'm a MERN/Full Stack developer, that means I'm responsible on developing the front end and the back end logic in my applications."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "How would you discribe yourself?",
                    "answer": "Since I was a child I've always been interested and feel curiosity in technology and computers, due to that I've found myself in sometroubles. Now as an adult I consider myself as a curious, responsible and loyal person."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "Why should we hire you?",
                    "answer": "As the way I see it, I find myself as someone with big potential. Besides, I always work to the fullest with the best energy and respect to everyone."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "Do you have any previous experience?",
                    "answer": "At this time I don't. Nowadays, speaking about my own, it is difficult find jobs oportunities due that most employers require people with experience."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "What technologies do you know?",
                    "answer": "I have knowledge using React (Redux, Router, Hooks), MongoDB, Express, NodeJS, SQL Server, MySQL and also PHP and ASP"
                  }
                ]
              },
              "education": {
                "header": "Academic Background",
                "data": [
                  {
                    "date": {
                      "start": "2022",
                      "end": "2022"
                    },
                    "title": "React Hooks, Redux, Router Course",
                    "where": "Udemy",
                    "status": "completed",
                    "average": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "date": {
                      "start": "2020",
                      "end": "2022"
                    },
                    "title": "Programming Senior Technician",
                    "where": "UTN FRGP, Argentina",
                    "status": "completed",
                    "average": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "date": {
                      "start": "2013",
                      "end": "2029"
                    },
                    "title": "Bachelor's Degree in Counting Administration",
                    "where": "Instituto Federico Dickens, Argentina",
                    "status": "completed",
                    "average": ""
                  }
                ]
              }
            }
          }
        }
      }
    }
  }